A Guide to the Virginia Municipal League Archives 1925-1989
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Drug/Alcohol Abuse and Control 1973-1976 (Box 54)
- Economic Concerns for the Elderly 1972-1982 (Box 54)
- Economic Development (N.D.) (Box 54)
- Education 1983-1984 (Box 54)
- Electric Franchises 1964-1972 (Box 54)
- Eminent Domain 1980 (Box 54)
- Employees 1982-1983 (Box 54)
- Environmental Issues 1986-1989 (Box 54)
- Environmental Policy Commission 1983 (Box 54)
- Environmental Quality Policy Committee 1990-1992 (Box 54)
- Environmental Society Meetings 1982 (Box 54)
- EPA Papers (N.D.) (Box 55)
- Erosion and Sediment Control 1991 (Box 55)
- Evans-Robb Report 1987 (Box 55)
- Fairfax County vs. Nassif 1979 (Box 55)
- Federal Aid Highway Program 1970-1974 (Box 55)
- Federal Budget Cuts 1986-1987 (Box 55)
- Federal Natural Gas Hearing 1957 (Box 55)
- Federal Urban Policy 1979-1981 (Box 55)
- Finance of Education 1977-1984 (Box 55)
- Fire Service 1982 (Box 55)
- Fringe Benefits 1970-1980 (Box 55)
- Garbage Collection 1955-1979 (Box 55)
- Gas 1966-1975 (Box 55)
- General License Taxes 1970-1975 (Box 55)
- General Revenue Sharing 1973-1983 (Box 55)
- General Revenue Sharing 1973-1978 (Box 55)
- Governor's Action Sessions 1991 (Box 55)
- Gramm-Rudman Committee 1986 (Box 55)
- Hazardous Waste Emergency Response 1980-1982 (Box 56)
- Health Risk Reduction Programs 1979-1981 (Box 56)
- House Joint Resolution 1986 (Box 56)
- HUD: Economic and Community Development 1977-1983 (Box 56)
- Industrial Revenue Bonds 1982-1987 (Box 56)
- Interlocal Cooperation and Annexation Issues 1988-1989 (Box 56)
- Jails and Correctional Facilities 1982-1983 (Box 56)
- James River Drought Study 1991 (Box 56)
- Journals of local Governmental Law 1986 (Box 56)
- Land Gains Tax 1974-1975 (Box 56)
- Land Use Court Cases 1975-1981 (Box 56)
- Landuse Planning 1975-1981 (Box 56)
- Law Enforcement 1975-1981 (Box 56)
- Lead-Drinking Water 1991 (Box 56)
- Leasehold Interest Taxation 1980 (Box 56)
- Legislation 1978 (Box 56)
- Legislative Committee Appointment 1982 (Box 56)
- Liability of Local Government Officials 1982-1983 (Box 56)
- Litter Control 1976-1979 (Box 56)
- Local Government Structures 1988-1989 (Box 57)
- Study of Local Government Interim Report 1977 (Box 57)
- Local Individual Income Tax 1971-1981 (Box 57)
- Local Medical Needs 1977 (Box 57)
- Local Ordinances 1972 (Box 57)
- Local Strategies for Conservation 1975-1979 (Box 57)
- Maintenance and Operation of Sewer Systems 1973-1977 (Box 57)
- Meal and Transient Room Tax 1976-1982 (Box 57)
- Medicaid and Medicare 1980 (Box 57)
- Motor Vehicle Use 1980 (Box 57)
- Municipalities in the United States Supreme Court 1986-1989 (Box 58)
- Municipal Ownership 1957-1974 (Box 58)
- National Institute of Municipal Law Officers 1987-1990 (Box 58)
- National League of Cities 1975-1976 (Box 58)
- National Resources: Development and Conservation 1974-1981 (Box 58)
- Noise Pollution and Control 1973-1981 (Box 58)
- Open Space 1970 (Box 58)
- Opening Costs and Finances 1973-1979 (Box 58)
- Other State Information 1978-1981 (Box 58)
- Payment in Lieu of Taxes 1978-1981 (Box 58)
- Pay Plans 1980-1981 (Box 58)
- Personal Grievances 1982-1983 (Box 58)
- Personal Statistics 1974-1975 (Box 58)
- Planning Commission 1982 (Box 58)
- Planning Legislation (N.D.) (Box 58)
- Police Cars and Motorcycles 1973 (Box 58)
- Population 1974-1981 (Box 58)
- Powhite Parkway: Legal File 1983 (Box 58)
- Precious Metals (N.D.) (Box 58)
- Primaries 1977 (Box 58)
- Private Sector Contracting 1981-1983 (Box 58)
- Procurement Specifics 1983 (Box 58)
- Productivity Improvement 1978-1981 (Box 58)
- Public Employee Bargaining 1975-1982 (Box 58)
- Public Employment and Manpower 1970-1985 (Box 58)
- Public Official Liability Insurance 1983 (Box 59)
- Public Service Corporation 1979 (Box 59)
- Public Transportation 1968-1981 (Box 59)
- Public Education 1983-1984 (Box 59)
- Railroads 1981 (Box 59)
- Rates Survey 1974 (Box 59)
- Real Estate Assessment Procedure 1982-1983 (Box 59)
- Real Property Taxation 1970-1978 (Box 59)
- Recent Court Cases 1984 (Box 59)
- Recycling 1973-1979 (Box 59)
- Rehabilitation Services 1979 (Box 59)
- Residence for Public Employees 1979 (Box 59)
- Revenue Bonds 1979 (Box 59)
- Revenue Sharing 1977-1982 (Box 59)
- Roads 1982 (Box 59)
- Sales Tax 1983 (Box 60)
- Sales Tax and Salary Survey 1975-1983 (Box 60)
- Single Family Mortgage Tax-Exempt Bond 1979-1981 (Box 60)
- Solid and Hazardous Waste Management 1978 (Box 60)
- Soil Conservation and Control 1970-1977 (Box 60)
- Sovereign Immunity 1982 (Box 60)
- Special Transportation 1973 (Box 60)
- Speeches and Articles (Clay) 1982 (Box 60)
- State Education Budgets 1978-1981 (Box 60)
- State Emergency Plan 1980 (Box 60)
- State Health Department 1975-1980 (Box 60)
- State Law Municipalities 1985-1989 (Box 60)
- State and Local Highway Programs 1963-1984 (Box 60)
- State and Local Taxation 1980-1984 (Box 60)
- State Strategies for Conservation 1980-1981 (Box 60)
- State Water Study Commission 1980-1981 (Box 60)
- Statutory Construction (N.D.) (Box 60)
- Storm and Surface Drainage 1972-1979 (Box 60)
- Street Lighting 1974-1979 (Box 61)
- Street Numbering Systems (N.D.) (Box 61)
- Street Opening and Grading 1972 (Box 61)
- Street, sidewalk, Curb and Gutter Policies 1973-1982 (Box 61)
- Street Use Regulation 1971 (Box 61)
- Subdivisions 1966-1978 (Box 61)
- Suits Against Local Government Officials 1983-1985 (Box 61)
- Sunday Closing Law 1982 (Box 61)
- Supreme Court Decisions 1983 (Box 61)
- Survey Model Code Service (towns) 1981-1982 (Box 61)
- Taxation of the Elderly 1973-1974 (Box 61)
- Taxation for Towns 1983-1984 (Box 61)
- Taxes 1978-1983 (Box 61)
- Miscellaneous on Tax Licenses 1967-1980 (Box 61)
- Taxicabs 1968-1972 (Box 61)
- Taxpayer Suits 1982 (Box 61)
- Teachers Salaries 1980-1983 (Box 61)
- Telephones (N.D.) (Box 61)
- Telephone Rate Case 1945 (Box 61)
- Testimony 1989 (Box 61)
- Tie Breakers 1982-1985 (Box 61)
- Tires 1989 (Box 61)
- Title XX 1978-1980 (Box 61)
- Torts 1981-1983 (Box 61)
- Torts Claim Act 1985-1987 (Box 61)
- Town Sales Tax (N.D.) (Box 61)
- Toxicity Monitoring 1985-1987 (Box 61)
- Traffic and Parking Regulations 1983 (Box 62)
- Training and Travel Policies 1969-1977 (Box 62)
- Transferable Development (N.D.) (Box 62)
- Transient Occupancy Tax 1982 (Box 62)
- Tree Cutting 1986-1987 (Box 62)
- Tree Preservation 1985 (Box 62)
- Truck Length and Width 1985 (Box 62)
- Unclaimed Property 1982 (Box 62)
- Underground Storage Tanks 1988-1989 (Box 62)
- Unemployment Compensation 1977-1980 (Box 62)
- Uniform Local Fiscal Reporting 1978-1983 (Box 62)
- Unsafe Buildings 1983 (Box 62)
- Uranium 1981-1985 (Box 62)
- Urbanization 1978 (Box 62)
- Urban 12 1970-1972 (Box 62)
- Utility Tax 1982 (Box 62)
- VDOT (transportation) 1987-1989 (Box 62)
- Vendors (N.D.) (Box 62)
- Video Games 1982 (Box 62)
- VA Public School Boards 1974-1982 (Box 62)
- VML Legislative Committee Meeting 1989 (Box 63)
- VML Legislative Programs 1981-1983 (Box 63)
- VML Publications 1988 (Box 63)
- VML-VACO Joint Committee 1977-1978 (Box 63)
- VML Safety Rules 1985-1986 (Box 63)
- VML-VACO Power Steering Committee 1988-1990 (Box 63)
- VML-VACO-VEPCO 1978 (Box 63)
- VML-VACO Intergovernmental Relations Task Force 1987-1988 (Box 63)
- VML-VACO-VEPCO Contracts 1979 (Box 63)
- Volunteer Programs 1973-1983 (Box 63)
- Waste Water Treatment 1978-1979 (Box 63)
- Water 1980-1983 (Box 63)
- Water Conservation 1946-1982 (Box 63.)
- Water Pollution and Control 1979-1983 (Box 63)
- Water Quality 1990 (Box 63)
- Water Works 1985-1991 (Box 64)
- Weapons 1981 (Box 64)
- Weed Abatement 1990 (Box 64)
- Welfare 1974-1976 (Box 64)
- Welfare 1974-1976 (Box 64)
- Workmen's Compensation 1962-1984 (Box 64)
- Workplace Conditions 1970-1983 (Box 64)
- Workshops: General Information, n.d. (Box 64)
- WTKR Editorials 1988-1989 (Box 64)
- Zoning: Extent of Local Power 1977-1983 (Box 64)
- Zoning, n.d. 1982-1983 (Box 64)
- Zoning Matters 1986-1988 (Box 64)
- Miscellaneous booklets and pamphlets (Box 65)
- Computerization and Information Systems 1973-1979 (Box 66)
- Structure and Organization 1979-1980 (Box 66)
- Federal and State Aid to Local Governments 1971-1982 (Box 66)
- General Social Services 1971-1981 (Box 66)
- Local Boards and Commissions 1968-1973 (Box 66)
- Local Finances 1972-1981 (Box 66)
- Metropolitan and Intergovernmental Relations 1967-1980 (Box 66)
- Publicly owned buildings, n.d. (Box 66)
- Regional Government and Special Districts 1965-1973 (Box 66)
- Salaries 1972-1985 (Box 66)
- System Analysis 1972-1974 (Box 67)
- Training Local Elected Officials 1981 (Box 67)
- Uniforms 1980 (Box 67)
- Municipal Safety Programs 1978-1980 (Box 67)
- Commission On Local Government 1980-1981 (Box 67)
- Double Taxation 1976-1980 (Box 67)
- Cost Containment 1978-1981 (Box 67)
- Long vs. the Town of Blacksburg 1979 (Box 67)
- Bailey vs. the Isle of Wright 1978-1979 (Box 67)
- Services and Programs 1981 (Box 67)
- General Revenue Sharing 1980 (Box 67)
- Biographies and Resumes 1970-1981 (Box 67)
- Newspaper and Press Releases 1973-1977 (Box 67)
- Sunbelts vs. Frostbelts 1976 (Box 67)
- Model City Programs 1971-1973 (Box 67)
- Citizen Participation in Government 1978-1981 (Box 67)
- Sovereign Immunity 1978-1980 (Box 67)
- Senior Citizens 1979-1980 (Box 67)
- Citizen Information 1981-1982 (Box 67)
- Affirmative Action in Richmond 1973-1980 (Box 68)
- Grievances Procedures 1973-1982 (Box 68)
- Pensions and Retirement 1970-1979 (Box 68)
- VSRS Study Commission 1979 (Box 68)
- VSRS Study Commission by JLARC 1972-1982 (Box 68)
- VSRS Study Commission (Minutes and Articles) 1978-1979 (Box 68)
- VSRS 1978-1979 (Box 68)
- Personnel Rules 1973-1979 (Box 68)
- Public Employee Bargaining 1973-1979 (Box 68)
- Public Employee Bargaining 1971-1974 (Box 68)
- Bicycles 1980-1981 (Box 69)
- Organization of Recreation Programs 1973-1976 (Box 69)
- Parks 1978-1981 (Box 69)
- Developments of Greater Than Local 1975-1977 (Box 69)
- Growth Management 1970-1976 (Box 69)
- Industrial Developments 1969-1979 (Box 69)
- Key Facilities 1975 (Box 69)
- Local Planning 1972-1974 (Box 69)
- Preservation of Agricultural Land 1974-1977 (Box 69)
- State Planning 1974 (Box 69)
- Federal Economic Assistance 1971-1980 (Box 69)
- Ports, n.d. (Box 69)
- Rural Developments 1977-1983 (Box 69)
- General Assembly 1973-1981 (Box 69)
- Legislation Affecting Local Government 1970-1980 (Box 69)
- State Budget 1976-1984 (Box 69)
- State Economic Assistance 1973-1983 (Box 69)
- State Mandates Affecting Local Government 1977-1982 (Box 69)
- State Mandates 1976-1981 (Box 70)
- Virginia Constitution 1927-1969 (Box 70)
- Initiative 1978-1980 (Box 70)
- Local Government Advisory Council 1980 (Box 70)
- Federal, State, Local Relationships 1978-1981 (Box 70)
- General Services, Purchases and Supplies 1978-1983 (Box 70)
- Abandoned of Illegally Parked Vehicles 1975-1979 (Box 70)
- Buslines 1972-1980 (Box 70)
- Interstate Highway 1979 (Box 70)
- Local/State Ahd 1978-1980 (Box 70)
- Maintenance and Repair of Roads 1961-1978 (Box 70)
- Parking 1973-1978 (Box 70)
- Annexation 1978-1990 (Box 70)
- Telephone Rate Case 1950, 1952, 1957-1958 (Box 71)
- Utility Rates 1963-1974 (Box 71)
- VEPCO Rate Case 1933, 1938, 1947, 1970 (Box 71)
- Joint Action Agencies 1979 (Box 71)
- Water Utilities 1976-1980 (Box 71)
- Water Rates for Non-Residents/Stafford vs. Fredericksburg 1978-1979 (Box 71)
- Municipal Utility Bills/Debuctibility Under IRS Regulation 1980 (Box 71)
- Tax and Expenditure Limitations (Box 72)
- Articles, Newsletters, and Booklets (Box 72)
- Billboards (Box 72)
- Community and Economic Development Policy Committee (Minutes, Notes, Agendas, Correspondence) 1986-1990 (Box 72)
- Community and Economic Development 1988 (Box 72)
- Drinking Water 1990-1991 (Box 72)
- Effective Govt. Committee 1988 (Box 72)
- Effective Govt. Policy Committee 1990 (Box 72)
- Environment Quality 1987-1990 (Box 72)
- Annexation, City Status, etc. 1977 (Box 72)
- Legislative Committee 1981 (Box 72)
- Population Growth and Development (Box 72)